http://www.medifocus.com/privacy.php?a=a

Medifocus.com Privacy Guarantee
Our Privacy Policy is really quite simple:
We respect yours.
If you need more detail than that, please read on.
At Medifocus.com, Inc.® we believe that customers like you deserve to be treated with the utmost respect. And that includes respecting your right to privacy. Here's how we guarantee that.
Data Collection and Storage
We've designed and structured our entire site so that you can visit and browse without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. The only way for us to obtain any personal information about you at all is for you to tell us yourself.
Cookies
Like most online merchants, our website uses "cookies" to enhance your online shopping experience. Cookies are just little packages of data that our server sends to your computer. They cannot tell us anything about you or your computer and no other website or server except ours can access the cookies we send. We don't permit our cookies to store personal or credit card information.
IP Address
Our server automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP Address and information about the page you have requested to view. This tells us which pages our customers are most interested in, and helps us tailor our site according to our customers' wants and needs.
How Your Personal Information Is Used
We use the information you provide, such as your name, mailing address and/or email address to answer any future questions you may have, or contact you regarding questions about your order. We might also email previous customers for feedback regarding their Medifocus Guidebook(s), and offer new products or special discounts from Medifocus.
Security of Your Information
At Medifocus.com, we have several security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information you provided. These measures include password protection, encryption and personnel reliability. For more information on these and other security measures, please see our detailed Security Policy.
How to Change Your Information or Opt Out
Occasionally we may Email you information from our partners about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. We respect your right to opt-out from our email list and once you "unsubscribe" we will remove your Email address from our list.
If you wish to have us remove your personal information from our databases, simply send a blank email with "unsubscribe" in the subject line to: unsubscribe@medifocus.com or mail your request to us at: Medifocus.com, Inc., 3809 Clarks Lane, Suite 100, Baltimore, MD 21215.
Changes to This Policy
We reserve the right to amend this policy as needed.
We Welcome Your Questions or Suggestions
If you have any questions about this Privacy Guarantee, the practices of our site, or your interactions with this website, please feel free to contact: info@medifocus.com.
© Copyright 1999-2020 Medifocus, Inc. All rights reserved as to the selection, arrangement, formatting, and presentation of the information contained in this report, as well as our background and introductory information.
Search
Acoustic Neuroma
Atrial Fibrillation
Carcinoid Tumors
Chronic Lymphocytic Leukemia
Chronic Pancreatitis
Ductal Carcinoma in Situ of the Bre
Lymphedema
Most Popular Guides:
Page Updated on:
April 30, 2020
`
